A Guide to the Farrier Family Papers, 1894-1972
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Box 28, 1921-1939 (Box 28)
  - Dunford, E. F. v. J. A. Conley, June 1930.
  - Gordon Dalton & Co., July 1928-November 1932.
  - Dillow, J. L. (claims against), December 1928-August 1932.
  - Dixie Chewing Gum Co. v. The People's Supply Co., January-April 1932.
  - Sears & Roebuck Co. v. Mrs. B. A. Duncan, January-February 1932.
  - Lambert Chemical Co. v. C. L. Harshburger, December 1931-November 1932.
  - J. H. Davidson v. W. V. Morris, admr., June 1931-July 1939.
  - Collection suits involving: Allen F. Eaton v. E. F. COnger; Eline's, Inc. v. L. E. Munsey; Gibson Candy Co. v. James A. Woods and Lucas; Giles County Motor Co. v. B. H. Taylor; and Lockwood Embree Sales Corp. v. Virginia Garage, March 1925-March 1932.
  - Childress, H. J. v. A. A. Atkins, October 1926-April 1927.
  - Cutherell, Milton v. Kropff and Ratcliff, January 1925-October 1926.
  - Giles Hardware Co., September 1926-April 1927.
  - Swinn and Brown v. Bal & Susie Napper, June 1924.
  - Swinn and Brown v. C. C. Thompson, June 1924.
  - Hare & Chase, Inc. v. E. M. Johnson, October 1928-June 1929.
  - Howery-Taylor Milling Co., June 1926-April 1927.
  - Hale, E. M. v. Miller Pocahontas Coal Co., September 1928.
  - Honaker, J. C., October 1928.
  - Mrs. Mack Harry vs. Floyd Owens, April 1928-January 1930.
  - Loose materials (numerous small claims suits), July 1925-July 1932.
  - Dr. H. G. Johnson vs. E. B. Chambers, October 1927-August 1928.
  - C. H. Johnson, December 1926-April 1927.
  - Jamison Motor Co. vs. Orrin and A. S. Vaught, January-February 1930.
  - R. P. Johnson, June 1927-December 1928.
  - Johnston Brothers, February 1927-March 1934.
  - Karm's vs. Mrs. Chas. T. Graham, January-April 1927.
  - Kiromac Mfg. Co. vs. J. L. Warren, December 1928-January 1932.
  - Long, A. B. v. J. W. Munsey, February 1926-September 1927.
  - Arthur Miller vs. L. D. Boyd.
  - G. T. Mason vs. W. A. Lucas.
  - L. L. Miller vs. Emmett Hutchinson, December 1924-February 1926.
  - Newport Merchantile Co. vs. Emmett Hutchinson, December 1924.
  - R. R. Moore and Co. vs. F. P. Snidow, February-November 1927.
  - W. T. Munsey vs. J. A. Woods, March 1927.
  - Maddox and Jennings Bakery Co. vs. W. L. Woods; Maddox and Jennings Bakery Co. va. F. R. Snidow, September 1927-February 1928.
  - McNutt Furniture Co. vs. various clients, July 1924-February 1928.
  - Several small claim collection suits, January 1925-November 1932.
  - Wiley Munsey vs. Roy C. Munsey, et al. August 1934-November 1939.
  - New River Merchantile Co. vs. W. R. Mallory, September 1926-February 1927.
  - Newport Service Station vs. Bill Deering, January 1928.
  - Napper, Susie, June-August 1927.
  - Newport Merchantile Co. vs. J. W. Porterfield, December 1931.
  - Narrows Motor Co. vs. Harry Hicks, June-July 1926.
  - Noel, J. S. vs. Shirley Munsey, November 1926-December 1927.
  - J. S. Noel vs. various claims, September-November 1928.
  - Oak Hill Garage vs. Blake Eaton, September-October 1930.
  - Pembroke Canning Co. vs. J. A. Woods, June-October 1926.
  - Pulaski Foundry and Mfg. Co. vs. C. H. Johnson, September 1924-July 1927.
  - Ferry-Morse Seed Co. vs. G. W. Painter, November 1933.
  - Paragon Cooperage Co. vs. New River Lime Co., December 1927-December 1928.
  - Preas, H. R., vs. various claims, January-August 1929.
  - National Biscuit Company vs. Buster Perdue, July-August 1931.
  - Porterfield, V. K. vs. various claims, May 1931-April 1932.
  - Oscar Perdue vs. William Perdue, July 1927-September 1932.
  - Rains vs. A. J. & Viola Blankenship.
  - Rome Soap Mfg. Co. vs Johnsons Steam Laundry, August 1928-January 1929.
  - Rich Creek Hardware Co. vs. L. M. Cooper, September 1926-November 1929. Radford Sales Corp. vs. W. A. Fletcher, May-June 1930. Rocky Gap Merchantile Co. vs. W. G. Kitts, July-October 1930. Rocky Gap Merchantile Co. vs. B. H. Barnett, July-October 1930. Catelberg Nation Jewelry Co. vs. Mrs. Carrie Rowe, September-October 1932. Rountree's Furniture Co. vs. W. N. Hurley, April-May 1933.
  - Roanoke Dry Goods Co. vs. Mrs. J. W. Johnson, March 1929-September 1932.
  - Roanoke Marble and Granite Co. vs. W. T. Turner, July 1929-March 1930.
  - Strange Construction Co., November 1928-January 1931; May 1929-June 1930.
  - Spear and Co. vs. Thomas Casey, November 1927-March 1928.
  - F. P. Snidow Co. vs. W. R. Mallory, May 1926.
  - Snidow Mfg. Co. vs. A. A. Atkins, March-April 1927.
  - Stovall, G. P. vs. J. R. Hale, April 1928-July 1929.
  - Spear and Co. vs. Earnest Perkins, September 1927. Spear and Co. vs. Minnie Blankenship, February 1928.
  - Straus and Schram vs. E. B. Stafford, January 1930.
  - Shelton and Shelton, various claims, January 1926-July 1927.
  - Stark Bros. vs. Earle Vaught, January 1928-July 1930.
  - Several small claim suits involving the following: J. E. Shcrader vs. J. H. Pruett; J. C. Shelton vs. M. T. McArthur; Seidman Neckware Co. vs. H. B. Shelton Co.; J. L. Sibold vs. T. L. Litchford; Spiegel vs. Burman Blankenship. November 1930-February 1932.
  - St. Elizabeth's General Hospital vs. Charley Davis, March 1925. St. Elizabeth's General Hospital vs. A. L. Webster, January 1929.
  - H. B. Shelton Co., various claims, July 1926-March 1928.
  - Several small claims involving the following: S. E. Stafford vs. H. D. Sands; F. P. Snidow and Co. vs. Floyd Kissinger; Shelton and Shelton vs. Thompson and Taylor; Shelton and Shelton vs. B. H. Taylor; Shelton and Shelton vs. W. B. Snidow; Dr. S. A. Tuck vs. Robert Jones; St. Clair vs. Gordon; St. Luke's Hospital vs. George Chapman, dec'd. January 1924-July 1932.
  - George Spangler vs. Mrs. D. T. Spangler, March 1930-August 1932.
  - Trent, B. W. vs. C. W. Kropff, July 1927-Mary 1928.
  - Thomas Merchantile Co., November 1927-September 1933.
  - Updyke, A. Z. vs. J. M. Muffley, July-August 1931.
  - Victory Specialty Co., various claims, July 1925-November 1928.
  - Walker and Scott, various claims, June 1925-May 1927.
  - Walker & Farrier Collections, January-December 1932.
  - Mrs. W. F. Wright, May 1927-July 1928.
  - Walker and Birk vs. Narrows Bottling Co., August-October 1928. Central Petroleum vs. Narrows Bottling Co., August-October 1928.
  - Mrs. W. A. Wilburn vs. C. H. Lankford, January 1928-September 1929.
  - Dr. Paul S. Williams vs. Roy Hardin, February 1930.
  - Walker Williams, December 1924-April 1931.
  - Warlick Furniture Co., various claims, October-November 1926.
  - Small claims involving the following: O. K. Caps vs. Wolf Creek Merchantile Co.; Witten, T. F. vs. D. M. St. Clair; Warlick Piano Rooms vs. J. H., E. N., and Marshal Williams; Bluefield Plate Glass vs. J. L. Warren; Montgomery Ward and Co. vs. H. W. Williams; National Biscuit Co. vs. Bob's Place. June 1931-July 1933.
  - Virginia Tarriffs, March 1926-August 1930.
  - Virginian Grocery Co., various claims, September 1929-January 1932.
- Box 29, 1926-1938 (Box 29)
  - Albert, Ernest vs. Virginia Department of Highways, July-December 1936.
  - Anderson, Tyler, July 1937.
  - Alvis vs. Johnson, April 1932-February 1938.
  - Collection suits, land transactions, or suits involving the following: P. F. Ball; Lewis Bowles; J. H. Brown; Buchanan Coal Land Corp. to Kingston Coal Co.; Clarence Brooks, et al to W. J. Brooks; T. W. Kerr to J. W. Bailey, et al; J. L Breeding to V. M. Breeding; G. O. Beckner; J. A. D. Bales to J. S. Andrews. January 1930-October 1937.
  - Blankenship vs. Hopkins, June 1935-February 1937.
  - Burnett vs. Price, November 1935-February 1936.
  - Croy vs. Croy, March 1929-September 1934.
  - Central Manufacturing Co. vs. C. W. Kropff, April 1936-August 1937.
  - Court cases, collection suits, deeds and unpaid bills involving the following: Caldwell Sites Co,.; Sidney Chewning; W.. Caudill; Eliza Comer vs. W. A. Comer; Mitchell Caudle; D. E. Conley; Mrs. Arch Caldwell; S. L. Creath; Lula Carter; Athrus Chambers; W. H. Calhoun; O. H. Cunningham; Cudahy Brothers Co.; Frank D. Claypool; Dode G. Caldwell; Henry Campbell; C. I. T. Corporation; Constantine L. Cametas. August 1935-March 1938.
  - Dublin Roller Mills vs. J. M. Martin; June 1927-November 1930.
  - P. K. Dickinson vs. Mrs. J. C. Meadows, et al, September 1933-May 1937.
  - Correspondence, court cases, collection suits, and deeds involving the following: John Draper; Frank S. Demsky; R. Frank Debusk; C. W. Dunford; Carey Dunn; Frank S. Douthat; Bessie E. Douthat,. November 1934-January 1938.
  - East River Grocery Co. vs. W. C. Simpkins, et al, October 1936-April 1937.
  - Court cases and collection suits involving the following: L. C. Epling; Tot Evans; Charley Farley. August 1934-June 1937.
  - Federal Forest Matters, August 1934.
  - French vs. Commonwealth.
  - Farewell vs. Farewell, September 1934-May 1937.
  - Farmers and Merchants Bank of Rich Creek, September 1935-March 1936.
  - Correspondence, court cases, collection suits, contract and deeds involving the following: J. W. Flannagan; Rocky Gap Flooring Co.; Hoge Hunter; Will Fuller; Farmers Exchange, Inc.; Federal Land Bank of Baltimore; Marvin Farley; Mrs. J. H. Fry; Everette Fletcher; Fidelity and Deposit Co. of Maryland; Theo. R. Ferrell; Harper N. Frei; George E. L. Fletcher. January 1936-February 1938.
  - H. E. Gilmer, July 1934-September 1936.
  - Court cases, collection suits, deeds, and correspondence involving the following: G. M. Hodge; Jack Harrell; Wilbur and Kemper Hale; Ransom B. Houchins; Frank Harless; H. F. Harless; Beulah Holland. February 1935-January 1938.
  - Harvey vs. Harvey, April 1936-April 1937.
  - Huff, Andrews and Thomas vs. Kate Wall estate, August 1932-September 1937.
  - Hardware Mutual Casualty Co.--Herbert Saphir, July-December 1934.
  - J. H. Howell vs. I. R. Lilly, November 1933-June 1936.
  - R. F. Hare estate-Walker A. Williams, adm., December 1928-January 1933.
  - Loose material for: H. S. Edmunds; I. G. Reed; J. W. Cunningham; Standard Oil Co.; A. Ray Johnston; R. King Johnston; Emory Johnston; John Jarney; Robert A. Johnston; Mrs. Earl G. Johnson; Mrs. Lucy Johnston. April 1930-May 1937.
  - P. M. Johnston, July-August 1934.
  - Wm. M. Johnston et al vs. Jasse E. Johnston et al, January-April 1937.
  - Loose materials: Guy Kost; L. A. Kessinger; Kimbalton Lime Co.; C. W. Kropff, September 1934-December 1936.
  - G. C.Kirk vs. Ida and Joe McCroskey, February 1936-January 1937.
  - A. L. Kingrea vs. Emory and Henry College, Inc., January 1934.
  - C. W. Kelly vs. B. H. Taylor, March 1925-November 1936.
  - Loose material: Cleo Lucas; Mrs. W. K. Leech; W. K. Lucas; Lon Link; Guy Lucas; D. O. Lawrence; Larkin Co., Inc.
  - G. A. Lucas vs. Porterfield, A. J., January-March 1937.
  - Lambert vs Lambert, July 1934.
  - J. B. McCracy Co., April 1934-January 1938.
  - Mountain Trust Bank vs. Warren Sarver estate, October 1934.
  - Paul Martin, September-November 1934.
  - L. E. Munsey vs. Lena Carter, October 1934.
  - Methodist Episcopal Church-Pearisburg, September 1934-August 1936.
  - F. A. and J. D. Meadows, March 1926-August 1937.
  - Loose material (in two files): J. C. Meadows; Montgomery Ward; Norton General Hospital vs. E. E. Martin; Paul Martin; E. J. and Talma Martin; Harry Martin; Lee Moyer; D. H. Martin; Virginia Munsey; Cora Kerr et al and William Mills; Mrs. Clyde Martin; Bernard Mason; W. H. Malcom; F. E. Martin; Ann Meadows; W. S. Meadows; C. M. McClung and Co.; Merchantile Adjuster Publishing Co.; E. R. McLear; Jack Martin; Mr. and Mrs. W. W. Mallory; Woody Nolen; A. J. Nackley; J. A. Newberry; Josie Perdue; A. J. Porterfield; Virgil Pennington; W. H. Quam; John H. Painter; Roy Richardson (Gov. G. C. Peery); C. A. Payson; Pure Oil Co.; S. L. and E. N. Peters; Walter Prunty; K. M. Messer vs. J. C. Perdue; W. D. Pearson; Star Amusement Co.; N. F. and M. B. Rowland; Ira Reed and the Rich Creek Supply Co.; Hugh N. Rakes; W. C. Rose and Co.; J. E. Robertson, et al; Mrs. T. F. Richardson; Tom Rock. December 1034-February 1938.
  - Price, Harold vs. Quality Produce Co., July-September 1934.
  - Rich Creek Water Co. vs. R. C. and F. H. Blankenship, September 1934-March 1935.
  - Serrill, George and Gertrude, October 1933-September 1934.
  - Loose materials: Roy Caudill Sadler; St. Elizabeth's General Hospital vs. H. H. Smallwood; Star Amusement Co.; George Sayers; Mrs. W. C. St. Clair; Robert Snider; George C. Spangler; B. H. Taylor: Ottomar Strange; W. E. Snider; E. E. Snidow; Snow Church Directory Co.; W. A. Snidow et al; H. M. Smith; J. T. Snidow; C. P., J. W., and P. F. Shrader; Maggie Songer et al; Simon Solins vs. P. W. Strother. June 1931-November 1937.
  - D. J. Smithson, April 1935-February 1938.
  - George H. Serrill, November 1931-October 1937.
  - J. J. Snidow, January 1933-August 1937.
- Box 30, 1916-1939 (Bulk, 1930-1939) (Box 30)
  - Application for retirement from the N & W Railroad by J. W. Taylor; J. W. Turner inquires as to her being named guardian of Woody Nowlin; contract between W. D. Tuggle and Elizabeth Tuggle. January-August 1937.
  - Ruth E. Turner vs. Beulah Mary Turner et al, November 1935-July 1936.
  - Correspondence, deeds, contracts, collections suits, and cases involving: J. W. Turner; Spear and Co. vs. S. A. Thompson; Young vs. B. J. Thompson; Howe, Cora and Medie Tabor; B. M. Teel vs. Joe Troitino; W. A. Thornhill; Theodore T. Thomas; University of Virginia. September 1934-January 1938.
  - Fay Vaught vs. Irene Vaught, March 1936-February 1939.
  - Wilburn, G. L. vs. Commonwealth.
  - Williams vs. Williams, July 1934-February 1935.
  - Martin Williams Land Bank Matter, March 1925-December 1934.
  - Wheeler, N. L. vs. Howard J. Lambert et al, April 1929-February 1935.
  - Martin Williams, estate, August 1934-January 1936.
  - Mary Woolwine Jones vs. John E. Jones, July-October 1934.
  - Deeds, wills, court cases, collection suits, or correspondence involving: W. R. Williamson; Julia Woodyard; L. C. Williams; Walkter A. Williams, I. E. Williams; Roy Witten; Charles Wilkenson; Claude Williams; George W. Wheeler; Mrs. Margaret Williamson; Harrison Woodyard; Martin Williams; J. W. Williams; W. F. Wright; J. W. Walker and Son; Roberta Shamson vs. T. B. Shannon; John Walker; A. C. Williams; R. H. Woods vs. J. E. Webb; Lewis Wall; F. H. Woods; Donald Williams and S.S. Williams; Fred Wells; L. C. Woodyard; Everette Wolf; Homer Wilson; J. H. Walker, Susie J. Walker; J. J. Wicker. July 1934-March 1938.
  - Notes on small claims collections suits, September 1916-January 1918.
  - Town of Pearisburg, July 1933-July 1934.
  - Town of Pearisburg, February 1932-January 1935.
  - Town of Pearisburg, October 1934-April 1936.
  - Blank legal forms (2 files).
  - Checkbook, August 1934-February 1937.
  - Walker Williams' notebook, May 1925-November 1936.
  - Blank forms.
- Box 31, 1915-1965 (Bulk, 1920-1939) (Box 31)
  - Atwood. Thomas, November 1927.
  - P. A. Albert, October 1924.
  - G. W. Albert, October 1924.
  - Bradberry, Samuel T. and Mary E. Burton.
  - Amanda and Washington Banks, October 1924.
  - Brown, A. P.
  - Breedlove, Harry W.
  - Buchanan, W. H., July 1924.
  - Butt, L. H., April 1931.
  - Blankenship, Ruthie C., May 1915-May 1919.
  - Blankenship, Macey.
  - Buchanan, T. Hoge, October 1919-January 1934.
  - T. A. J. Braton Estate, May 1940-November 1965.
  - Eva B. Carter, July 1924-February 1925.
  - Croy, David J, et al, September 1922.
  - W. T. Cuddy, October 1924.
  - Crumb, A. J., July 1924.
  - E. E. and J. J. Cook, September 1924-May 1925.
  - Coburn, Mrs. Kate, May 1925.
  - Harvey B. Croft, May 1916-July 1923.
  - Croy, A. E., May 1916-November 1927.
  - Charlton, Newtonia H., July-October 1916.
  - W. G. Carter, October 1924.
  - Cunningham, F. H. and L. E.
  - Crawford, John C.
  - Dulaney, D. E., June 1922.
  - Dunagan, J. Clyde.
  - Deaton, J. N., June 1934.
  - Dowdy, Roy F., August 1926-August 1939.
  - Eaton, John T., February 1925.
  - Emma Eaves, July 1924.
  - Eaton, W. P., February-November 1917.
  - Eaton, Boyd.
  - Eaton, A. M., et al.
  - Epling, J. H.
  - Epling, Moses and Sons, May 1922.
  - Epling, E. E. and B. F., December 1920-December 1929.
  - Fletcher, Joseph W., October 1919.
  - Fanning, Wm. H., March 1917-March 1920.
  - Ferrell, Ezekiel, June 1917.
  - French, Cecil T., December 1922.
  - Fletcher, G. E., September 1940.
  - Fletcher, George E., October 1939-June 1950.
  - Gans, C. L., February 1918.
  - Gilmer, Charles H., December 1922.
  - Gillespie, D. E., May 1918-June 1924.
  - Goodwin, J. R., October 1924.
  - Hale, H. W., July 1917.
  - Hughes, A. F., March 1925-April 1932.
  - Henderson, Charles E., et al.
  - Harvey, James L. and wife, 1950.
  - Hopkins, E. A., July-October 1934.
  - Hutchinson, Woodie C., May-June 1922.
  - Marshal Harris, July 1924-June 1930.
  - Holt, F. C., August-December 1928.
  - Honaker, J.D. estate, et al, September 1926-April 1927.
  - Hurt, A. G., July-August 1924.
  - Hetherington, G. W., November 1919.
  - Hare, R. F.
  - Hendrickson, O. F., August 1922-November 1933.
  - Hickerson, J. L., May 1925-November 1933.
  - Johnston, R. A., October 1924.
  - Johnston, J. D. and Shumate, March 1924-January 1925.
  - Johnston, J. D. (heirs).
  - Johnston, J. Raleigh, April 1937.
  - Johnston, W. L. and wife, December 1933.
  - Johnston, T. Cover, June 1917-September 1934.
  - Jennell, E. C., January 1934-August 1939.
  - King, T. B.
  - King, W. B., August 1917.
  - Kinzie, W. L., December 1933-March 1940.
  - King, C. C., July-September 1924.
  - Kanode, Nancy P. and Gilbert L., July 1933-August 1934.
  - Julia Hale and Lushbaugh.
  - Long, O. L., et al, July 1924.
  - Lambert, C. F.
  - Lovell, E. O., February 1924.
  - Mason, Clay, March 1918-November 1928.
  - Mustard, J. R. and wife.
  - Morton, C. T., October 1924.
  - Moltox, P. C., October 1924.
  - Munsey, G. Ed. G., July 1926.
  - Porterfield, C. G. and wife, November 1933.
  - Porterfield, A. R., et al, February 1916.
- Box 32, 1904-1960 (Bulk, 1920-1939) (Box 32)
  - Porterfield, Andrew J., August 1923-September 1941.
  - Porterfield, A. F, W. H., and I. G., October 1959.
  - Parker, Mary E., August 1960.
  - Pack, A. E., July 1924.
  - Porterfield, V. K.
  - Powell, J. Alex, June 1917-November 1929.
  - Robertson, Emmons B., June 1943.
  - Raines Land, April 1924-February 1926.
  - Robertson, H. D., December 1921-October 1922.
  - Reynolds, C. P., June 1924.
  - Robertson, Grady.
  - Radcliff, Joseph, February 1928.
  - Rogers, W. H., June 1925.
  - Ratcliff, J. B., January 1925.
  - Runion, Albert, July 1924.
  - Robertson, Josie A.
  - Robertson, John T.
  - Robertson, Marvin L.
  - Spangler, B. H., January-May 1925.
  - Snidow, W. L. and A. W.
  - Sublett, Minnie J, August 1925-October 1927.
  - Snidow, G. G., August 1926.
  - Simcox, F. Ray, January 1927.
  - Songer, Nelson, estate, April-June 1929.
  - Short, W. P., July 1924.
  - Stafford, E. W. July 1924.
  - Snidow, Lacy B., January 1931.
  - Snodgrass, W. P., October 1924.
  - St. Clair, Miss Mary E.
  - Shelton, H. B., March 1918.
  - Stafford, P. C.
  - Scott, Fred and wife.
  - Shumate, K. R. and S. E. Lucas, June 1916.
  - Strother, J. F., August 1928-November 1929.
  - Snidow, J. M.
  - Smith, W. A. and T. M.
  - Schrader, Lockard A.
  - Shelton, H. B., May 1918-September 1922.
  - Stanley, J. S., April-May 1925.
  - Stafford, Frank K., et al, September 1912-August 1933.
  - Shrader, R. L., November 1921-March 1941.
  - Tuggle, J. C., September-December 1929.
  - Turner, T. E., et al, April-May 1920.
  - Sarver, C. E., October 1924.
  - Williams, Isaac E., May 1939-April 1940.
  - Virginian Railway Company abstracts, December 1923-July 1924.
  - Wheeler, C. B.
  - Wilburn, Mrs. Joane.
  - Warner, J. P., January-March 1940.
  - Williams, Samuel W., March-April 1920.
  - Wilson, Ed., July 1924.
  - Williams, O. G., October 1924.
  - Woolwine, C. R., June 1924.
  - Williams, A. E., August 1924.
  - Williams, A. S.
  - Walker, John F.
  - Williams, R. L., April 1929.
  - White, J. A. and Elizabeth, October 1924.
  - Williams, G. S., October 1924.
  - Wysong, John E., June 1904-December 1922.
- Box 33, 1913-1971 (Box 33)
  - Bowles, C. J., December 1920-February 1943.
  - Crowgey, W. P., August 1926-November 1960.
  - Linkous, R. T., August 1926.
  - Copies of deeds, contracts, and abstracts, January 1934-May 1948.
  - Star Amusement Co., Inc., January 1959-January 1971.
  - Surratt, Harry M (FHA), May-September 1951.
  - Stafford, J. R. estate, November 1933-July 1965.
  - Stafford, Walter W., April 1950-April 1952.
  - Snodgrass estate, November 1949-May 1950.
  - Stare Amusement Co. vs. Taylor and Sons Co., May 1954.
  - Songer, Wirt (GI Loan), August 1955-May 1956.
  - Shepherd, Wm. J.
  - Shomo, Ronald E. and wife (FHA), August-September 1960.
  - Stebar, Opel R., et al, vs. Russell F. Stebar, March 1953-January 1954.
  - Shumate, Rufus H,, May 1954-September 1966.
  - Turner, Kenneth V., June 1953.
  - Williams, Billie L, August 1958-October 1960.
  - Wolfe, Ada Calcutt, estate, December 1960-June 1962.
  - Whittaker, Blanche G., May 1964.
  - Franklin Real Estate Co., February 1931.
  - Highway Commission vs. L. D. Shumate, November 1926-July 1928.
  - Killey, P. H., November 1929-November 1939.
  - Whittaker and Carr vs. S. U. Vermillion, October 1929-October 1934.
  - O. W. Danner vs. D. M. Bruce, May 1933-October 1934.
  - Strother, D. J. F. vs. Mary C. Painter, September 1928-October 1933.
  - Clay Mason estate, November 1928-October 1933.
  - Park, Karl C., October 1931.
  - Robertson, Tyler S., June-December 1929.
  - Roller, J. E., March 1925-May 1935.
  - Reynolds, Howard M, June 1929.
  - H. B. Shelton and Co., February 1915.
  - Saunders, C. A., January 1915.
  - Smith, E. B., May 1913.
  - Straley, C. F., September 1918-October 1925.
  - Tuggle, J. C., October 1928-July 1936.
  - Williams, C. N., march 1934-March 1955.
  - French, George F., June 1927-January 1934.
  - Vaught, Leonard C., August 1930.
  - Sarver, J.Wm., October 1927.
- Box 34, 1915-1972 (Bulk, 1940-1969) (Box 34)
  - Breedlove, Nannie, April 1938-June 1940.
  - Caudill, W. C., et al, June 1939-October 1940.
  - Carper, Frank W., September 1943-December 1949.
  - Francis, T. B., December 1937-May 1950.
  - Hale, H. W., December 1915-May 1945.
  - Hopkins, E. A., et al, May 1941-January 1946.
  - Horton, E. W., September 1938-November 1950.
  - Ingram, R. M., June 1943-January 1946.
  - Johnston, King and R. A., September 1945-May 1950.
  - Johnston, Ed. B., December 1942-June 1943.
  - Johnston, J. C. and J. R. Jr., April 1943.
  - Johnston, A. Ray and C. I., April 1943-February 1945.
  - Kessinger, Raymond H, June 1946.
  - Correspondence, deeds, and maps relating loans and land transactions: S. J., J. H., and D. H. Walker; Harvey B. Wilson, et al to C. V. Wilson; D. W. Sanders to Ernest Hilton; Harry M. Douthat; Pearisburg Methodist Church; Morton King; Jack Turner; Noble D. Porterfield to T. M. Smith; C. B. Gilliam to the First Methodist Church of Pearisburg; J. L. Morris; E. H. Dillon, et al to R. C. Dillon. October 1929-December 1971.
  - State Highway Commissioner vs. Turner, December 1970-November 1971.
  - Davis, Billy N., October-December 1970.
  - Kirby, Donald L. and wife, September-December 1970.
  - Estep, Cecil J. and wife, March-April 1971.
  - Hobbs, Franklin D. and wife, June 1966-May 1971.
  - Brown, Gray Jr., March-April 1971.
  - Tawney, Alfred L. and wife, October-November 1970.
  - Thomas, W. B.; Quesenberry, F. C.; and Riddle, W. H., June 1967-October 1971.
  - Caldwell, James E. and Frazier, Robert W., October 1967-November 1970.
  - Condrey, Ida P., September-November 1971.
  - Deck, Charles M. and wife, October-November 1971.
  - Fisher, William G. and wife, February-April 1972.
  - Davis, Thomas H and wife, July-September 1971.
  - Day, Dewey E. and wife, July 1971. Mann, H. W. and wife, May 1972.
  - Farmer, Roger N. and wife, March-April 1972.